Agnish Chakraborty

Freelance chatbot and back-end expert.

I am an experienced software developer with a strong knowledge and open mind to find solutions to difficult problems. Hard working, creative, quick learner. Specialise in thinking out side the box and creating new ways to solve problems. Productive with teams and single developer scenarios.

agnishc.dev@gmail.com

8906877505

Kolkata, India

16 March, 1997

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Developer and Consultant NYC Travel Buddy

01/2019 - Present

NYC (Offshore)

NYC Travel buddy is a chatbot that is powered by AI and is helping users find restaurants, show points of interest and find events.

Achievements/Tasks

- Built the chatflow and design.
- Built a custom Natural Language Understanding module.
- Integrated 12+ APIs to power the recommendation engine.
- Integrated 3+ social platforms to interact with the chatbot.

Chatbot and Blockchain Developer Upwork

01/2019 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

- Achieved the top rated developer title on the platform.
- Completed 19 jobs in the first six months.
- Have a job success rate of 100%.
- Requirement analysis and understanding of new business logic.

Developer and consultant

Omikron Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

06/2018 - 01/2019

Kolkata

Private software development firm specialising in modern web and software development.

Achievements/Tasks

- Lead a team of three to complete various projects.
- Completed 15+ projects.
- Worked on fields of chatbots and blockchain.
- Requirement analysis and understanding of new business logic.
- Client management.

Chatbot developer TokenPay

04/2018 - 01/2019

Romania (offshore)

Achievements/Tasks

- Developed a customer support chatbot for the blockchain based company.
- Built using dialogFlow API and custom webhooks.
- Created more than 800+ intents to support all the questions.
- Integrated telegram bot framework to interact with the chatbot.

SKILLS



LANGUAGES

English

Bengali

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

WORK EXPERIENCE

Blockchain developer Ahol Sniffs Ethereum Project

02/2018 - 03/2018

Kolkata

Achievements/Tasks

- Built a payment processor using blockchain.
- Built smart contracts in solidity for payment verification.
- Integrated the payment backend with the website built by esolz technologies.
- Payment support for e-commerce.

Blockchain and chatbot InternEsolz technologies

01/2018 - 03/2018

Kolkata

Achievements/Tasks

- Created 3+ smart contracts using solidity on the ethereum blockchain.
- Created a experiment chatbot for automation of job enquiry.
- Contributed to 2 website development project.

EDUCATION

B.Tech

Narula Institute Of Technology